Guide to the School of Hotel Administration Associate Dean for Academic Affairs records, 1982-2005.
School of Hotel Administration Associate Dean for Academic Affairs records
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
School of Hotel Administration Associate Dean for Academic Affairs records, 1982-2005.
28-1-2411
Cornell University. School of Hotel Administration. Associate Dean for Academic Affairs.
26 cubic feet.
Correspondence, printed materials.
Division of Rare and Manuscript Collections, Cornell University Library
Includes reports, committee meeting minutes, correspondence, publications, and subject files pertaining to curriculum development and the Associate Dean for Academic Affairs Office.
COLLECTION DESCRIPTION
Includes reports, committee meeting minutes, correspondence, publications, and subject files pertaining to curriculum development and the Associate Dean for Academic Affairs Office.
SUBJECTS
Names:
Cornell University.; Cornell University -- Faculty.
Subjects:
Hotel management schools -- New York (State) -- Ithaca.
INFORMATION FOR USERS
Access Restrictions:
Restricted to permission of the office of origin.
Closed for research until 2016.
CONTAINER LIST
- External Programs, 1980's (Box 1)
- Aruba (Box 1)
- Brazil (Box 1)
- Caribbean (Box 1)
- Dominican Republic (Box 1)
- ESSEC (Box 1)
- Glion (Box 1)
- Ivory Coast (Box 1)
- Korean Tourist Association (Box 1)
- Mexico (Box 1)
- Nigeria (Box 1)
- China (Box 1)
- Portugal (Box 1)
- Puerto Rico (Box 1)
- Gambia (Box 1)
- Singapore (Box 1)
- Minutes of Various Meetings, 1980-1987 (Box 2)
- Curriculum Committee, 1979-1980 (Box 2)
- Guest Lecturers, 1977-1986 (Box 2)
- Faculty Search: Real Estate/Project Development Advertisements (Box 3)
- Faculty Search: Real Estate/Project Development Search Plan (Box 3)
- Faculty Search: Managerial Communications (Box 3)
- Faculty Search: Quantitative Methods (Box 3)
- Faculty Search Committee Minutes and Correspondence, 1974-1980 (Box 3)
- Research Project Descriptions (Box 3)
- American Express Foundation (Box 3)
- Herrmann - "Steamtable Pan Tong Research" (Box 3)
- White - "Comparative Waste Disposal Methods" (Box 3)
- Penner - "Hotel Planning: Typical Guest Room Floor" (Box 3)
- Eyster/Geller - "Capital Budgeting Techniques" (Box 3)
- Moore - "Guest Room Energy Conservation" (Box 3)
- Geller - "Uncapitalized Financing Leases" (Box 3)
- Herman - "Investigation of Grievances" (Box 3)
- Clark - "Energy Usage Research" (Box 3)
- Goodman - "Use of Critical-Incident Methodology to Waiter/Waitress Training" (Box 3)
- Durocher - "Food Service Industry 2001" (Box 3)
- Sherry - "Legal Aspects of Travel and Tourism" (Box 3)
- Cantwell/Chase - "Expansion and Reconstruction of CU Restaurant Simulation" (Box 3)
- Eyster - "Statistical Decision Theory Applied to Hotel Overbooking Problems" (Box 3)
- DeRoos - "Energy Consumption Modeling Program" (Box 3)
- Ferguson - "Economic Impact of the Employee Retirement Income Security Act of 1974" (Box 3)
- Eyster - "Cash Flow Management Procedures in Use in Hotel Industry" (Box 3)
- Burtt/Geller - "Survey of Hedging in Hotel Industry" (Box 3)
- Tabacchi/Goldstein - "Survey of Hedging in Hotel Industry" (Box 3)
- Mutkoski/Redlin - "Cooking Meat in Bags in Water" (Box 3)
- Eyster/Geller - "Capital Budgeting Techniques in the Hospitality Industry" (Box 3)
- Geller - "Uncapitalized Financing Leases - Debt? (Box 3)
- Berger/Bronson - "Entrepreneurs in the Hospitality Industry" (Box 3)
- Moore/Bernstein - "Entrepreneurs in the Hospitality Industry" (Box 3)
- Tabacchi/Heist - "Nutritional Adequacy of Hotel Menus" (Box 3)
- Beals - Critical Review of Hotel Feasibility Studies" (Box 3)
- Arnaldo - "Appraisal of Hotel General Managers" (Box 3)
- Tabacchi/Schneider - "Industry Use of Frozen Bread Dough/Functional Properties of Gluten" (Box 3)
- Wasmuth/Davis - "Management Study" (Box 3)
- Chase - "AMEX - Transportation Census" (Box 3)
- Kaven/Eyster - "Analysis of the US Domestic Hotel Management Contract Agreements" (Box 3)
- Memos and Correspondence (Box 3)
- Seddik Serghini - Marrakech, Morocco (Box 3)
- Vipin Suri - New Delhi, India (Box 3)
- Professor Mrs Yang Ja Yoo - Seoul, Korea (Box 3)
- Hideaki Tanabe - Miyanoshita, Hakone, Japan (Box 3)
- Correspondence on Japanese Students Seeking Admission (Box 3)
- Jose Nobre Vieira Hannheman (Box 3)
- Naoto Kojima (Box 3)
- Jochen Langer - West Germany (Box 3)
- Motohiro Ochi (Box 3)
- Correspondence on Korean Students Seeking Admission (Box 3)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1974 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1974-1975 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1975-1976 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1976-1977 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1977-1978 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1978-1979 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1981-1982 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1982-1983 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1983-1984 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1984-1985 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1985-1986 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1986-1987 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Instructions, 1948 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1987-1988 (Box 4)
- Practice Credit Committee Files, 1988-1989 (Box 4)
- Research Committee, Pre-1988-1989 (Box 5)
- Research Projects, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
- Research Projects, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
- Research Projects, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
- Research Requests, 1988 (Box 5)
- Research Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 5)
- Research Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 5)
- Research Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 5)
- Research Committee, 1988-1989 (Box 5)
- Research Director Search, 1992 (Box 5)
- Past Committees, 1986-1990 (Box 5)
- Renovation - School and Hotel (Box 6)
- Fall Courses, 1989 (Box 6)
- Spring Courses, 1990 (Box 6)
- Scheduling (Box 6)
- Miscellaneous Ad Hoc Committees (Box 6)
- Associate Deans Working Group, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
- Associate Deans Meeting, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
- Associate Deans Meeting, 1991-1992 (Box 6)
- Curriculum Committee, 1989-1990 (Box 6)
- Curriculum Committee, 1990-1991 (Box 6)
- Curriculum Committee, Pre-1988-1989 (Box 6)
- Curriculum Review Task Force (Box 6)
- Statler Teaching Interns (Box 7)
- Graduate Program (Box 7)
- Graduate Committee (Box 7)
- Graduate Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
- Graduate Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
- Graduate Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 7)
- Graduate Faculty Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
- Faculty Meetings, 1990-1991 (Box 7)
- Faculty Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 7)
- Faculty Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 7)
- Newsletter, 1990-1991 (Box 8)
- Newsletter, 1991-1992 (Box 8)
- Newsletter, 1992-1993 (Box 8)
- Newsletter, 1993-1994 (Box 8)
- ADBA Search, 1990 (Box 8)
- GA's, 1987-1990 (Box 8)
- TA's, 1987-1992 (Box 8)
- IBM Grant (Box 8)
- IBM Hand held POS (Box 8)
- Short Term Suggestions-Budget Cuts (Box 8)
- Annual Reports (Box 8)
- Academic Integrity (Box 9)
- Academic Deficiency (Box 9)
- Area Coordinators, 1989-1990 (Box 9)
- Full Professors, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Minority Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Committee on Academic Records and Registration, 1991-1993 (Box 9)
- Area Representatives, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Faculty Policy Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 9)
- Area Coordinators, 1990-1991 (Box 9)
- Human Relations Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- Faculty Policy Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- Associate Dean's Meeting, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- Staff Meetings, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- IS Steering Committee, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- Information Services, 1992-1993 (Box 9)
- Human Relations Committee, 1993-1994 (Box 9)
- Staff Meetings, 1994 (Box 9)
- Curriculum Committee Review - Documents and Minutes, 1982-1988 (Box 10)
- Faculty Policy Committee History Information, 1990 (Box 11)
- Associate Deans Group, 1987-1989 (Box 11)
- Curriculum, Pre-1990 (Box 11)
- Computer Needs, 1992 (Box 11)
- Staff Meetings, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Minority Affairs Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Faculty Policy Committee, 1991-1992 (Box 11)
- Miscellaneous Actions (Box 12)
- Faculty Meetings, 1993-1994 (Box 13)
- Faculty Meetings, 1994-1995 (Box 13)
- Faculty Meetings, 1995-1996 (Box 13)
- Annual Report, 1991 (Box 13)
- Disclosure Forms, 1996 (Box 13)
- Academic Leadership Service, 1994 (Box 14)
- Area Reps, 1992-1994 (Box 14)
- Associate Deans, 1993-1997 (Box 14)
- Full Professors, 1993-1995 (Box 14)
- Research Committee, 1993-1995 (Box 14)
- FPC, 1993-1994 (Box 14)
- Beth Carlson Ganem - Better Living Concept, 1991 (Box 14)
- Petition Minutes (Box 14)
- World Tourism Organization, 1991 (Box 14)
- Human Relations Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
- 100 Level Required Courses (Box 14)
- Academic Records and Registration Committee (Box 14)
- Graduate Committee, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
- FPC, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
- Area Reps, 1994-1995 (Box 14)
- Research Proposals (Box 15)
- Syllabi (Box 16)
- Hotel Ezra Cornell Historical Files, Including Managing Directors Club (Box 16)
- Faculty Meeting Minutes, 1932-1979 (Box 16)
- Retired Faculty or Faculty Who Have Resigned: (Box 17)
- Arbel (Box 17)
- Bryson (Box 17)
- Chinloy (Box 17)
- Choi (Box 17)
- D'Aprix (Box 17)
- Rogers (Box 17)
- Gasser (Box 17)
- Jones (Box 17)
- Kayantas (Box 17)
- Levy (Box 17)
- LaFleur (Box 17)
- Merberg (Box 17)
- O'Connor (Box 17)
- Owens (Box 17)
- Moore (Box 17)
- Rice (Box 17)
- Richmond (Box 17)
- Suri (Box 17)
- Wissink (Box 17)
- TA Files (Box 18)
- Strategic Plan, 1993 (Box 18)
- Academic Integrity Files (Box 18)
- Old Committee Academic Policy (Box 18)
- Addition and School Renovations, 2001 (Box 19)
- Admissions Updates Dean Bishop (Box 19)
- Archives and Records Management Program (Box 19)
- Annual Reports (Box 19)
- AMP (Box 19)
- Anheuser-Bush Foundation (Box 19)
- American Management Association (AMA) (Box 19)
- American Hotel and Motel Association (Box 19)
- American Dietetic Association (Box 19)
- Americans Disability Act Project (Box 19)
- American Hotel Foundation (Box 19)
- American Assembly of Collegiate Schools of Business (Box 19)
- Alumni Career Advisory Network (Box 19)
- Alumni Affairs (Box 19)
- Alcohol Policy Statement (Box 19)
- Affiliation Agreement Framework (Box 19)
- Airline Antitrust Litigation, 1992 (Box 19)
- Antitrust Compliance Program (Box 19)
- Area Representatives - Topics for Discussion (Box 19)
- Articles Submitted (Box 19)
- Office of Assemblies (Box 19)
- Don Bishop Meetings (Box 19)
- Buckley Amendment (Box 19)
- Campus Code of Conduct (Box 19)
- Capital Campaign (Box 19)
- SHA Catalogs (Box 19)
- Center for International Studies (Box 19)
- Center for the Environment (Box 19)
- Certified Hospitality Educator (Box 19)
- Educational Institute Research Alliance (Box 20)
- Economics Interim Search (Box 20)
- General Manager Search, 2002 (Box 20)
- Guest Lecturers, 1987 (Box 20)
- Guns, Germs, and Steel Orientation Student Discussion (Box 20)
- Harassment Advisor (Box 20)
- Hotel School Advisory Board (Box 20)
- Instructional Quality Surveys, 1993-1994 (Box 20)
- Presidential Research Scholars (Box 20)
- Professional Development Program (Box 20)
- Professional Masters Program (Box 20)
- Promotion to Full Professor (Box 20)
- Proposed New Require Core for BS Degree, 1997 (Box 20)
- Reaccreditation Self Study (Box 20)
- Recommendation Letters (Box 20)
- Records Retention (Box 20)
- Religious Observances (Box 20)
- Research Grants (Box 20)
- Research Proposals, 2002 (Box 20)
- Salary Surveys (Box 21)
- Search Reports Completed (Box 21)
- Scholarship Proposal: Charles S. Chadwick (Box 21)
- Settlement Agreements and Full Release (Box 21)
- SHA Addition and Renovation (Box 21)
- SHMAI (Box 21)
- Society of Minority Hoteliers (Box 21)
- SODEXHO (Box 21)
- Southwest State University - Marshall, Minnesota (Box 21)
- Speeches (ANG) (Box 21)
- Staffing Levels (Box 21)
- Stakeholder Analysis (Box 21)
- State Education Department Review (Box 21)
- Strategic Plan, 1990 (Box 21)
- Terrorist Attack Tragedy, 2001 (Box 21)
- The Cornell Tradition (Box 21)
- The Gourman Report (Box 21)
- Tracking Study (Box 21)
- Tenure and Promotion (Box 21)
- Undergraduate Core Faculty (Box 21)
- Undergraduate Enrollment - Donald Bishop (Box 21)
- VIP Visits (Box 21)
- Visiting Faculty and Visiting Scholars (Box 21)
- ADAA Singapore/NTU Negotiation Files (Box 22)
- CNI Dean Contract, Term Sheet and Final Contract Negotiations (Box 22)
- IMHI/ESSEC Historical File, 1993-2005 (Box 23)
- Norwegian School - Stavanger College Historical File (Box 23)
- Chinese University of Hong Kong, 1990-2003 (Box 23)
- Curriculum Review, 1982-1984 (Box 24)
- No Box List Available (Box 25)
- No Box List Available (Box 26)